[
    { "question" : "चलना", "answer" : "to walk", "pronunciation" : "/tʃəlna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "बोलना", "answer" : "to speak", "pronunciation" : "/bolna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "जाना", "answer" : "to go", "pronunciation" : "/dʒana/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "खाना", "answer" : "to eat", "pronunciation" : "/kʰana/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "पीना", "answer" : "to drink", "pronunciation" : "/pina/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "रहना", "answer" : "to stay", "pronunciation" : "/raɦna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "सोना", "answer" : "to sleep", "pronunciation" : "/sona/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "उठना", "answer" : "to wake up", "pronunciation" : "/ʊʈʰna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "पढ़ना", "answer" : "to read", "pronunciation" : "/pʌdʰna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "लिखना", "answer" : "to write", "pronunciation" : "/likʰna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "बैठना", "answer" : "to sit", "pronunciation" : "/bɛʈʰna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "देखना", "answer" : "to see", "pronunciation" : "/dekʰna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "सुनना", "answer" : "to listen", "pronunciation" : "/sunna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "समझना", "answer" : "to understand", "pronunciation" : "/səmdʒʰna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "बताना", "answer" : "to tell", "pronunciation" : "/bətaːna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "सोचना", "answer" : "to think", "pronunciation" : "/sotʃna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "मिलना", "answer" : "to meet", "pronunciation" : "/milna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "होना", "answer" : "to happen", "pronunciation" : "/ɦona/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "जानकारी", "answer" : "to know", "pronunciation" : "/dʒaːnkaːriː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "भूलना", "answer" : "to forget", "pronunciation" : "/bʱulna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "याद रखना", "answer" : "to remember", "pronunciation" : "/jaːd rakʰna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "चलाना", "answer" : "to operate", "pronunciation" : "/tʃalaːna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "संभलना", "answer" : "to take care", "pronunciation" : "/səmbʰalna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "धोना", "answer" : "to wash", "pronunciation" : "/d̪ʱona/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "सजाना", "answer" : "to decorate", "pronunciation" : "/sədʒana/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "समय बिताना", "answer" : "to spend time", "pronunciation" : "/samae̯ bit̪aːna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "उपयोग करना", "answer" : "to use", "pronunciation" : "/ʊpəjoɡ kərna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "साफ करना", "answer" : "to clean", "pronunciation" : "/saːf kərna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "तैयार करना", "answer" : "to prepare", "pronunciation" : "/t̪aɪjaːr kərna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "लड़ना", "answer" : "to fight", "pronunciation" : "/laɽna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "हँसना", "answer" : "to laugh", "pronunciation" : "/ɦəsna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "रोना", "answer" : "to cry", "pronunciation" : "/rona/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "खरीदना", "answer" : "to buy", "pronunciation" : "/kʰariːdna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "बेचना", "answer" : "to sell", "pronunciation" : "/betʃna/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "आग लगना", "answer" : "to catch fire", "pronunciation" : "/aːɡ laɡnaː/", "part_of_speech" : "verb" },
    { "question" : "घर", "answer" : "house", "pronunciation" : "/ɡʱar/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "पानी", "answer" : "water", "pronunciation" : "/paːni/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "खाना", "answer" : "food", "pronunciation" : "/kʰaːna/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "कपड़ा", "answer" : "clothes", "pronunciation" : "/kəpɽaː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "माँ", "answer" : "mother", "pronunciation" : "/maː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "पिता", "answer" : "father", "pronunciation" : "/pɪtaː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "दोस्त", "answer" : "friend", "pronunciation" : "/d̪ost/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "पुस्तक", "answer" : "book", "pronunciation" : "/pustak/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "समय", "answer" : "time", "pronunciation" : "/samaɪ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "सुबह", "answer" : "morning", "pronunciation" : "/suba:h/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "शाम", "answer" : "evening", "pronunciation" : "/ʃaːm/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "रात", "answer" : "night", "pronunciation" : "/raːt/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "दिन", "answer" : "day", "pronunciation" : "/din/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "महिला", "answer" : "woman", "pronunciation" : "/məhilaː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "पुरुष", "answer" : "man", "pronunciation" : "/pʊrʊʃ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "बच्चा", "answer" : "child", "pronunciation" : "/batʃtʃaː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "स्कूल", "answer" : "school", "pronunciation" : "/skuːl/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "कॉलेज", "answer" : "college", "pronunciation" : "/kɔːleɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "शहर", "answer" : "city", "pronunciation" : "/ʃahar/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "गाँव", "answer" : "village", "pronunciation" : "/ɡaːɳv/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "सड़क", "answer" : "road", "pronunciation" : "/səɽak/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "नदी", "answer" : "river", "pronunciation" : "/nadiː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "समुद्र", "answer" : "sea", "pronunciation" : "/samundar/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "तालाब", "answer" : "pond", "pronunciation" : "/taːlaːb/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "बाग़", "answer" : "garden", "pronunciation" : "/baːɡ/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "कमरा", "answer" : "room", "pronunciation" : "/kamraː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "दुकान", "answer" : "shop", "pronunciation" : "/d̪ʊkaːn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "बाज़ार", "answer" : "market", "pronunciation" : "/baːzaːr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "फल", "answer" : "fruit", "pronunciation" : "/phal/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "सब्जी", "answer" : "vegetable", "pronunciation" : "/səbziː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "मछली", "answer" : "fish", "pronunciation" : "/matʃli/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "तेल", "answer" : "oil", "pronunciation" : "/teːl/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "राशन", "answer" : "ration", "pronunciation" : "/raːʃan/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "चाय", "answer" : "tea", "pronunciation" : "/tʃaːj/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "कॉफी", "answer" : "coffee", "pronunciation" : "/kɔːfiː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "पान", "answer" : "betel leaf", "pronunciation" : "/paːn/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "पौधा", "answer" : "plant", "pronunciation" : "/paʊdʱaː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "फूल", "answer" : "flower", "pronunciation" : "/phuːl/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "आधार", "answer" : "identity", "pronunciation" : "/aːd̪ʱaːr/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "चेहरा", "answer" : "face", "pronunciation" : "/tʃeːhraː/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "आँख", "answer" : "eye", "pronunciation" : "/aːŋkh/", "part_of_speech" : "noun" },
    { "question" : "अच्छा", "answer" : "good", "pronunciation" : "/acchaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "बुरा", "answer" : "bad", "pronunciation" : "/buraa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "बड़ा", "answer" : "big", "pronunciation" : "/baDaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "छोटा", "answer" : "small", "pronunciation" : "/choTaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "अधिक", "answer" : "more", "pronunciation" : "/adhik/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "कम", "answer" : "less", "pronunciation" : "/kam/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "सुंदर", "answer" : "beautiful", "pronunciation" : "/sundar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "पुराना", "answer" : "old", "pronunciation" : "/puranaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "नया", "answer" : "new", "pronunciation" : "/nayaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "जल्दी", "answer" : "fast", "pronunciation" : "/jaldii/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "धीमा", "answer" : "slow", "pronunciation" : "/dhiimaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "बहुत", "answer" : "very", "pronunciation" : "/bahut/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "थका", "answer" : "tired", "pronunciation" : "/thakaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "खुश", "answer" : "happy", "pronunciation" : "/khush/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "दुखी", "answer" : "sad", "pronunciation" : "/dukhii/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "मस्त", "answer" : "great", "pronunciation" : "/mast/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "स्वस्थ", "answer" : "healthy", "pronunciation" : "/svasth/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "बीमार", "answer" : "sick", "pronunciation" : "/biimaar/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "तंग", "answer" : "tight", "pronunciation" : "/tang/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ढीला", "answer" : "loose", "pronunciation" : "/dheela/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "अलग", "answer" : "different", "pronunciation" : "/alag/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "समान", "answer" : "same", "pronunciation" : "/samaan/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "शीतल", "answer" : "cool", "pronunciation" : "/shiital/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "गरम", "answer" : "hot", "pronunciation" : "/garam/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ताजा", "answer" : "fresh", "pronunciation" : "/taajaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "सुखा", "answer" : "dry", "pronunciation" : "/sukhaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "नम", "answer" : "wet", "pronunciation" : "/nam/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "भारी", "answer" : "heavy", "pronunciation" : "/bhaarii/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "हल्का", "answer" : "light", "pronunciation" : "/halkaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "महंगा", "answer" : "expensive", "pronunciation" : "/mahangaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "सस्ता", "answer" : "cheap", "pronunciation" : "/sastaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "सफ़ेद", "answer" : "white", "pronunciation" : "/safed/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "काला", "answer" : "black", "pronunciation" : "/kaalaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "लाल", "answer" : "red", "pronunciation" : "/laal/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "हरा", "answer" : "green", "pronunciation" : "/haraa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "नीला", "answer" : "blue", "pronunciation" : "/neelaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "पीला", "answer" : "yellow", "pronunciation" : "/peelaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "गुलाबी", "answer" : "pink", "pronunciation" : "/gulaabee/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "भूरा", "answer" : "brown", "pronunciation" : "/bhuuraa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "ग्रे", "answer" : "grey", "pronunciation" : "/grey/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "चमकीला", "answer" : "shiny", "pronunciation" : "/chamakilaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "मैदानी", "answer" : "plain", "pronunciation" : "/maidanii/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "मोटा", "answer" : "fat", "pronunciation" : "/motaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "पतला", "answer" : "thin", "pronunciation" : "/patlaa/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "गुलाबजामुन", "answer" : "sweet", "pronunciation" : "/gulaabjaa mun/", "part_of_speech" : "adjective" },
    { "question" : "अभी", "answer" : "Now", "pronunciation" : "/abhī/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आधेरे से", "answer" : "Slowly", "pronunciation" : "/ādherē sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आगे", "answer" : "Ahead", "pronunciation" : "/āgē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आकर्षक रूप से", "answer" : "Attractively", "pronunciation" : "/ākarṣak rūp sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आजकल", "answer" : "Nowadays", "pronunciation" : "/ājakal/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अगले", "answer" : "Next", "pronunciation" : "/aglē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अचानक", "answer" : "Suddenly", "pronunciation" : "/achānak/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अच्छी तरह से", "answer" : "Well", "pronunciation" : "/acchī tarah sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अत्यधिक", "answer" : "Excessively", "pronunciation" : "/atyadhik/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अधिकतम", "answer" : "Maximum", "pronunciation" : "/adhikatam/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अधिक", "answer" : "More", "pronunciation" : "/adhik/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अवश्य", "answer" : "Definitely", "pronunciation" : "/avaśya/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आसानी से", "answer" : "Easily", "pronunciation" : "/āsānī sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अलग-अलग", "answer" : "Different", "pronunciation" : "/alag-alag/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आधुनिकता से", "answer" : "Modernly", "pronunciation" : "/ādhunikatā sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अनुमान लगाकर", "answer" : "Presumably", "pronunciation" : "/anumān lagākar/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आसानी", "answer" : "Easily", "pronunciation" : "/āsānī/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अभी तक", "answer" : "Until now", "pronunciation" : "/abhī tak/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अविश्वसनीय रूप से", "answer" : "Unbelievably", "pronunciation" : "/aviśvasanīya rūp sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अत्यंत", "answer" : "Extremely", "pronunciation" : "/atyant/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अविश्वसनीय", "answer" : "Unbelievable", "pronunciation" : "/aviśvasanīya/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आत्मविश्वास से", "answer" : "Confidently", "pronunciation" : "/ātmaviśvās sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अक्सर", "answer" : "Often", "pronunciation" : "/aksar/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अच्छा", "answer" : "Good", "pronunciation" : "/acchā/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अशांत", "answer" : "Restless", "pronunciation" : "/aśānt/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आमतौर पर", "answer" : "Usually", "pronunciation" : "/āmatōr par/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अलग", "answer" : "Separate", "pronunciation" : "/alag/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "आराम से", "answer" : "Comfortably", "pronunciation" : "/ārām sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अच्छी तरह", "answer" : "Well", "pronunciation" : "/acchī tarah/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अभावपूर्ण रूप से", "answer" : "Absent-mindedly", "pronunciation" : "/abhāvpūrṇ rūp sē/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "अविरत", "answer" : "Continuously", "pronunciation" : "/avirat/", "part_of_speech" : "adverb" },
    { "question" : "और", "answer" : "and", "pronunciation" : "/aur/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "लेकिन", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "/lekin/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "या", "answer" : "or", "pronunciation" : "/ya/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "कि", "answer" : "that", "pronunciation" : "/ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जब", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/jab/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "अगर", "answer" : "if", "pronunciation" : "/agar/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "तो", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/to/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "क्योंकि", "answer" : "because", "pronunciation" : "/kyonki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जैसे", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "/jaise/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जहाँ", "answer" : "where", "pronunciation" : "/jahan/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जबकि", "answer" : "whereas", "pronunciation" : "/jabki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इसलिए", "answer" : "therefore", "pronunciation" : "/isliye/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "कुछ", "answer" : "some", "pronunciation" : "/kuch/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "की तरह", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "/ki tarah/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इस लिए", "answer" : "so", "pronunciation" : "/is liye/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इसके बाद", "answer" : "after this", "pronunciation" : "/iske baad/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जैसा", "answer" : "like", "pronunciation" : "/jaisa/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इस समय", "answer" : "at this time", "pronunciation" : "/is samay/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जितना", "answer" : "as much as", "pronunciation" : "/jitna/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "तब", "answer" : "then", "pronunciation" : "/tab/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जिसे", "answer" : "whom", "pronunciation" : "/jise/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "ताकि", "answer" : "so that", "pronunciation" : "/taki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "किसी भी", "answer" : "any", "pronunciation" : "/kisi bhi/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "बिना", "answer" : "without", "pronunciation" : "/bina/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "क्यों", "answer" : "why", "pronunciation" : "/kyon/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इस तरह", "answer" : "in this way", "pronunciation" : "/is tarah/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "कभी", "answer" : "sometime", "pronunciation" : "/kabhi/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जबसे", "answer" : "since", "pronunciation" : "/jabse/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जैसे कि", "answer" : "as", "pronunciation" : "/jaise ki/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जिसके बारे में", "answer" : "about which", "pronunciation" : "/jiske bare mein/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जहां तक", "answer" : "as far as", "pronunciation" : "/jahan tak/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "क्या", "answer" : "what", "pronunciation" : "/kya/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "कब", "answer" : "when", "pronunciation" : "/kab/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "तब से", "answer" : "since then", "pronunciation" : "/tab se/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "क्योंकि यह", "answer" : "because it", "pronunciation" : "/kyonki yah/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इसके लिए", "answer" : "for this", "pronunciation" : "/iske liye/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इससे पहले", "answer" : "before this", "pronunciation" : "/isse pahle/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इस बारे में", "answer" : "about this", "pronunciation" : "/is bare mein/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "कैसे", "answer" : "how", "pronunciation" : "/kaise/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "जो", "answer" : "which", "pronunciation" : "/jo/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "अभी", "answer" : "now", "pronunciation" : "/abhi/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "इससे बाहर", "answer" : "outside of this", "pronunciation" : "/isse bahar/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" },
    { "question" : "किन्तु", "answer" : "but", "pronunciation" : "/kintu/", "part_of_speech" : "conjunction" }
]